{
    "subject": "Michael_Dowse",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "It's_All_Gone_Pete_Tong",
    "human_readable": "Michael Dowse created the film It's All Gone Pete Tong.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.942589282989502,
            "question": "Who created the film It's All Gone Pete Tong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6327217817306519,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Michael Dowse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6289041638374329,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of 'It's All Gone Pete Tong'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6010730266571045,
            "question": "What genre might the film 'It's All Gone Pete Tong' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5495612025260925,
            "question": "What year was 'It's All Gone Pete Tong' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5446438789367676,
            "question": "Has Michael Dowse directed other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5075029730796814,
            "question": "Is Michael Dowse a film director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49824053049087524,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in 'It's All Gone Pete Tong'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47491219639778137,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films directed by Michael Dowse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46547573804855347,
            "question": "Where might I be able to watch 'It's All Gone Pete Tong'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Dowse created the film It's All Gone Pete Tong.",
            "html": "yago_9017_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in films directed by Michael Dowse?",
            "html": "yago_9017_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in 'It's All Gone Pete Tong'?",
            "html": "yago_9017_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Michael Dowse a film director?",
            "html": "yago_9017_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9017_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9017_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9017_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9017_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9017_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9017_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9017_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9017_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9017_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9017_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I will evaluate whether the triple \"Michael Dowse created the film It's All Gone Pete Tong\" is correct.\n\nHere are the results of my evaluation:\n\n- The text mentions that \"It's All Gone Pete Tong\" is a 2004 mokumentary / comedy film directed & written by Michael Dowse. (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9017/re-ranker-msmarco/85.txt)\n- The text further describes the film, mentioning that it was directed and written by Michael Dowse. (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9017/re-ranker-msmarco/57.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9017/re-ranker-msmarco/65.txt)\n- The text also provides information about the film's director, Michael Dowse, in various other contexts. (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9017/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9017/re-ranker-msmarco/57.txt)\n\nGiven the consistent information across multiple documents, I conclude that the triple \"Michael Dowse created the film It's All Gone Pete Tong\" is correct.\n\nTherefore, my response will be:\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Michael Dowse and his film \"It's All Gone Pete Tong,\" confirming that he was involved in its creation."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}